[{"answer": "Got it", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I understand", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I understand", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I'm sure", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Walk him over to that place, buy him an ice. It'll kill twenty minutes", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Tough...  ...I get off duty at fiv", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Greatest..", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Show..", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Show..", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "On earth", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " What", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " Don't say that! I don't want to hear you say that", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " Don't say that! I don't want to hear you say that", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Me?! You want me to take care of Billy?", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "He is...  You sat in that coffee shop across from schoo", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " You've been living here, in the city", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " What do you have here, my friend", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Have you ever been to that place", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " that place", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " No. But I've been to that place", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " What about your mommy", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " Do you like to be with your mommy", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " He hits me on the planet Kriptarium, when I steal the buried treasure from the famous peanut butter factory", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "  My daddy doesn't hit me, silly. Why would my daddy hit me", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Mrs. my friend, did you ever work in a job while you were married to your e", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Did you wish to", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " No", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " At the moment I am unemployed", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " Was there apple juice when you were little", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Was there Burger King", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Yeah, there was apple juice", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Uh, uh. There was no such a thing as Burger King", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Was there Burger King", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "What else wasn't there", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Bigger than a principal. The judge sits in robes in a big chair... The judge has thought a lot about us, about you and me and your mom, and he has decided...  ...he has decided that it would be best for you to live with your mom my friend in her apartment.  And I'm very lucky. Because even though you'll live with your mom my friend I'll get to see you once a week for dinner and a couple of weekends a month", "docId": "Kramer-vs-Kramer.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " What don't you understand, pal", "qsentId": 38}]